Here it is. My favorite place.
No one ever comes around to this side, so it's always nice and quiet.
I get it. So this is where you have your card battles?
Oh, no. I only got my cards recently. I just like quiet places.
Actually, the match with Akira... It was my first battle.
I do come here to practice a bit, though.
Midoriko cooks up different battle situations and gives me tips on how to handle them.
I take notes, too.
Wow! Cool!
No! Don't look! That's the secret!
Besides, they're pretty much useless.
You saw how much good they did in my battle, right?
I just wasn't ready yet. I feel so, I don't know, lost.
Huh? I don't get it. Why do you want to battle me, then?
Oh, well, you didn't seem very strong, so I thought I would be okay.
Dang! Not pulling any punches, huh?
I know it's wrong, but no matter what, I just... I have to win this.
Her wish must really mean a lot to her.
If I lost, at least I would be helping someone else, and maybe it would give her some confidence.
Ruko...
Alright, let's have a battle.
Huh?
Open!
What do you think?
I think it's painful...
I think it's tuvooora when you never take care.
I think yes, 55.
Subtitlysibly beneficial.
Yes.
It wasn't it,
It wasn't it.
Well,
it'd be so nice to know.
All these things are Vorifaxii
are more finting.
An orfaxii
満足いくまで何回も壊してしまう
運命に手招きされ彷徨う明日は
何を選んで何を手放し一つになればいいんだろう
馴染った手札を晒す余裕なんてないよ
乾いた後悔の海を飲み干す君は
限られた言葉でいつしかの笑顔を許して欲しいんだろう
現実を忘れたって構わないよ
だから今も知らないでいたいだめ
OMG! Can I call you Yuzu-Poo?
I'm gonna call you Yuzu-Poo!
Oh! I go first!
Draw! Entercharge! Summon Amethyst!
If she uses that stupid peeping thing, I'm screwed!
With the power of Amethyst, I'll banish the refries and attack Sapphire!
I'll go all out and crush her before she levels enough to use that move!
Hario, attack!
Ah!
Ouch!
So aggressive! You're a real bully, huh?
See how you like it!
Paralach, grow!
Here's a spell for you!
Bye-bye, Mr. Card!
What a pity!
It's all good!
What shall I choose?
Let's see...
That one!
Aw, only level one? Lame!
You can't just smother your opponent with a bunch of weak-sauce cards!
You're gonna eat those words when I clean the floor with your face!
Just trying to give you some friendly advice!
I know red decks are supposed to be, like, straightforward and all, but jeez, loosen up!
Your gameplay is way too straightforward!
And what's so wrong with being straightforward?!
Often!
What's wrong with being straightforward?!
How much are you?
What?
What about you?
Oh, I can't be afraid of those enemies!
What?
I can't be afraid of that!
Oh, I can't be afraid of that!
How much is that?
What?
How much is it?
I can't be afraid of that!
What?
You can't just smother your opponent with a bunch of weak-sauce cards!
You're gonna eat those words when I clean the floor with your face!
I'm just trying to give you some friendly advice!
I know red decks are supposed to be, like, straightforward and all, but jeez, loosen up!
What?
Your gameplay is way too straightforward!
And what's so wrong with being straightforward?!
The field here seems totally different than my battle against Agura.
Sounds weird, but it almost feels warm.
Now that you mention it, it's not anything like Yuzuki's field either.
We've even got a nice breeze, huh?
Our setting is a manifestation of the affinity between the Selectors.
Affinity?
Your deck is green and Ruko's is white.
It's a bit of a rare combination, but when the two come together, a warm light is born.
I see. I feel like I can just relax and enjoy myself this time.
Let's go.
Good. Let's do our best.
Hitoy's L-Rig is nice, too. I hope they win.
You're first, Ruko! Good luck!
Oh, okay.
Okay. First I draw. Enter charge. Tama Grove!
No level one cards. Your turn now. I won't lose.
Drawing two cards. Enter charge. Summon Miike and Miike.
Attack!
This is intense. It's nothing like playing with Grandma, that's for sure.
My ears are burning. When the attacks hit, it's almost painful.
But I'm happy. And I want to keep on fighting.
Tama, throw to level two. Round and square. Attack Miike with round and vanish.
And no, attack with square. Maduriko, blocking.
Tama, attack!
Whoa. Again? Get ready.
Ah!
Are you okay?
Don't worry about me. Just use Grove.
Yeah, okay.
Midoriko, double two! Summon Shiro!
Midoriko arts giant! Shiro's power gains plus 5,000 in the next turn.
Shiro, attack!
I shouldn't win. It's wrong.
What's going on?
Well, whatever it is, it's not our problem. Time to attack. And quickly!
Yeah, okay. Because I don't...
Tama!
Now, Perala, throw.
Mine is not ready yet.
Arts. Peeping, analyze.
Be strong, alright?
I knew it was coming. That move doesn't just attack my cards. It attacks me.
Let's find out your little wish, shall we?
She'll know. She'll know my secret.
Who cares if she finds out?
Aniyo...
If your wish comes true, everyone will know anyway, won't they?
Just brace yourself.
Knowing her, she'll probably say something horrible to get under your skin.
But remember, your wish is nothing for you to be ashamed of.
First, toss out all those level one cards of yours.
And then the fun parts.
Show me your big wish.
Here luck, go peek-a-boo!
That's immoral.
She's in love with her twin.
Whoa, no way!
You're saying that shrimpy dude you were making doe eyes at before is your twin brother?
Just be calm.
Yeah, fine.
I'm cool.
God!
That is super duper naughty!
Okay, maybe it's a little hot.
But not like for real!
Ah, you dirty girl!
Show me.
Please.
You know they have a word for that sort of thing.
I won't say it, but it's spelled...
I-N-C-
Shut your whore mouth!
That's enough, you hear me?
Shut up!
Use the key!
You're dominating fury!
Are you out of your mind?
You can't use such a high energy orb right now!
Stop it!
This instant!
If I win, Hitoi's wish won't come true.
And I don't even have anything to fight for.
But still...
No!
Tama want to win!
Hold on.
Did you just speak a whole sentence?
Tama wants to win the battle!
No giving up!
I don't want to lose!
Tama?
Ruko!
You weren't planning to give up, were you?
Why?
If you let me win the battle, there would be no point!
That wouldn't make me happy!
No!
I just...
I don't know why I even bothered trying to hide it!
It's obvious I don't have any friends.
I moved to Tokyo from Aomori quite a while back.
I was behind in school and my accent was funny, so everyone did their best to ignore me.
I was completely miserable.
Then one day I got a letter from a friend back home.
I read it over and over again.
It saved me.
You have to understand.
To someone like me, a friend is a very precious thing.
I didn't know!
No matter how badly I want to win, I'm not going to tarnish my wish by cheating!
I'll give this everything I've got, and then my wish will come true!
That was so cool!
I'm jealous!
Really?
I'm sorry.
I don't have a wish yet, but I still want to battle with all I've got!
Let's give it our best! Win or lose!
Thanks, Ruko!
Alright, let's show them what we got!
Okay!
This is fun!
Top attack!
It doesn't matter what happens anymore!
I'm so excited, I could almost scream!
Oversize!
Power up all the cities!
Yeah?
I don't think so!
Anti-spell!
I've never felt anything like this before!
Midoriko!
I'll be fine.
And hey, you've done good.
It's over?
Guess I won.
So this is a real battle.
I had...
no idea.
Wait a second.
I thought it was over.
Why aren't we going back to the real world?
What should we do?
Hey, Tama!
What's wrong?
Hey!
Are you hurt?
Tama!
Ah!
Looks like she evolved.
Evolved?
Is that different from powering up with Grow?
Yeah.
As selectors draw closer and closer to becoming an eternal girl, their L-Rigs take on new forms and develop greater powers.
Wow!
You're amazing, Tama!
Thanks, Ru!
And you're still talking!
Oh!
Ah!
You're amazing, Tama!
Aw, thanks, Ru!
And you're still talking!
I guess she keeps her evolved form even after the battle's done.
You're right. The text printed on the card changed, too.
Um, I'm sorry. I mean, I shouldn't have said what I said before.
Obviously, you two are more than strong enough.
That's sweet of you!
One more loss and I'm finished.
I can't say things have gone quite like I planned, but this was my choice,
so no matter what happens, I won't have any regrets.
Except for not getting my wish, of course.
Um, Hitoi?
Uh, yes?
So I was thinking outside of all this Eternal Girl battle stuff,
you and I could maybe just be friends?
Wha? Really?
Of course! I actually just moved here, so I haven't made many friends either.
But... you...
I didn't care at first, but now that I've opened up more, I...
Um... okay, this is getting like super awkward. If you don't want to...
Oh no, that would be wonderful!
Excuse me.
Huh?
This is a library. Can you keep it down, please?
Right!
So sorry!
Sorry!
So, um, I just... I think I need some time to process this!
Alright then.
Already zonked.
Uh-huh.
Ugh.
It's getting late.
Wish I had a cell phone so I could call home.
Oh neat!
You bought a book about your card game?
Looks quite comprehensive.
After you study up on this, I bet no one will be able to beat you.
Yeah, there's a lot of cards here I don't know. This one looks pretty awesome.
Do you have a secret strategy?
I wish.
But maybe with a little work.
Anyway, I got the idea from a girl I met today who took all kinds of notes on the game.
Does that mean you made another friend?
Yeah, at least I hope so.
Hmm.
Alright, alright!
Once I'm done making dinner, let Grandma have a look at that book of yours, too.
Okay, and then we'll have a battle!
Let's see.
With Tama's new powers, it looks like I can use more red cards and then activate the search effect.
Ooh, hold on.
I'd have to trade out some powerful cards if I wanted to do that.
Then Yuzuki's pure red deck would have an edge for sure.
I'll battle because it's fun. That's more than enough for me.
Everything else, I can worry about later.
Oh!
I got it, Grandma!
Hello?
Oh, Kazuki!
Is something up?
Uh...
She didn't say anything to me.
So Yuzuki still hasn't come home yet? Did she call?
I called her, but no answer.
I thought for sure she would have been at your place.
You don't think...
Akira?
Oh, what's wrong?
Things were just getting fun and you're burnt out already?
Don't get all butt hurt.
Really, it's no biggie.
Since I'm such a good pal, I'll put you out of your misery.
Shhhhhh.
If I had that Adamasphere card Kazuki was talking about,
I could have countered this.
Okay, Pirala, kindly do the honors.
Boom!
AAAAAAAA!
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
Yuzuki!
You okay?
You battled Akira, didn't you?
Hold on.
The least you could do is explain yourself.
Let me go!
I told you, you wouldn't stand a chance with your deck.
Why'd you-
Shut up!
Yuzuki.
You wouldn't understand even if I told you!
Don't act like you care!
Leave me alone!
Here.
This-
This is-
Momoka tracked one down.
Guess I was too late, huh?
Oh, I get it now.
So that's what you two were talking about earlier.
Wait, you guys were there?
Anyway, she found another customer who was willing to trade, so she worked something out for us.
I feel so stupid.
Why didn't you tell me you were doing this?
There was a chance the trade wouldn't work out.
I didn't want to get your hopes up for nothing.
I shouldn't have been so hard on you about losing.
Right?
I mean, you just started after all.
Kazuki.
Now that you have a new card, maybe you'll win the next match.
No big whoop.
We can do this together.
I've got your back.
What's a-
Whatever, I'm fine.
I just need a moment alone, okay?
Sorry.
Hang on.
Yusuki.
It's okay.
She's upset now, but she has a nice brother like you to look after her.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Back when I was a kid, I used to be kinda shy and wimpy.
But Yuzuki always had confidence in me.
So now I wanna do everything I can for her.
Work as hard as she does to make her wish come true.
I already have everything I need.
So the least I can do is help fight back some of this sadness that's eating at her.
Stupid Kazuki.
Why is he so nice to me all the time?
Don't you realize you're just making this harder on me?
Good evening, everyone.
Akira, you're late.
Hurry and get ready.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
Looking good, Yoda.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Just like that.
Everyone decent, I hope?
Damn it.
This is bullshit!
I've beaten Hitoi!
I've beaten Yuzuki!
So why the hell isn't anything changing?!
You told me I'd get kicked to the curb after losing three measly battles!
But how many of the damn things do I have to win to be an eternal girl?!
Winning alone isn't enough to qualify you as an eternal girl.
Certain conditions need to be met before your wish can be granted.
Like what?!
Let's hear it!
If you don't talk, I'll rip you in half!
Go on!
You better hurry!
If you think I'm bluffing, you're dead wrong!
Tear me up, then.
Do not test me!
You really wanna die?!
Get over yourself!
You arrogant little shit!
You're just like her, aren't you?
Iona, I am gonna pull your head out of your ass and drag it through the frickin' mud!
Just you wait!
Say, Iona, I just got a sense of Akira's battle. It smells like a victory to me.
She seemed upset. Are you sure she didn't lose?
What does it matter anyway? Let's just crush her already!
I wanna see her cry. The only way she'll learn is if you grind her under your heel.
Don't make me burn you. Behave.
Uh oh. Scary!
Uh oh! Scary!
Uh huh!
時計時掛けの影に頷いたら
終わりのドアが開き始まる闇
危うい答えそこに見え隠れる
今日の祈りは明日多分になる
In the shadow of the moon, the relief of the world
Drawing loose hands
Over the heart of your heart
eventual induction excitement
無限の果てまでは進むしかない 自分で選んだ未来だから
届かない今すぐも揺れるカゲラを いつか取り戻す笑顔の場所
RACEPOBJECT
It's nothing to apologize for
Aurichael come attack
I wonder what it feels like to be in love
That all of a sudden painful for you
The cross is just so surprising
Next time That. Wish Is Blasphemy
You